I was so excited that I wondered if it was a dream.
I didn't think it was a comedy camp.
It's about 6:00 p.m.
Yeah, about 6:00.
Oh my God, I'm going to die!
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you for watching.
I won't get up until the end, until the end, until the end.
Why is he so cute?
I guess it's the limit of the original
Cute.
Lis
Squirrel.
Lis.
Doing the work of the doer
Much, much more.
Much less.
Less.
Fewer.
Various members
Please move. Move number one.
Ten seconds left.
Look forward to it.
Bri-bri-bri.
You're so cute, Princess.
I don't know what's wrong with me
I'm so hungry
I asked her to marry meI asked her to marry me.
We're good friends.
Nice to meet you.
He's so cute.
You were so cute at the end.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
Oh!
He came in first.
Why are you doing this?
Why?
It looks good on you.
Bring the camp.
Uh, roller.
Lawler.
Sure thing.
Talk about still coming through.
Look.
How did you get caught?
Me?
Sudden urgency.
Oh,
I slipped on a creek.
It's a tiny...
It's a website.
I don't know...something
I put my face on the election poster.
Awww!
Aww...
of
Oyster
Buber's awesome glitter is being made and made!
I'm not sure what's going to happen yet, and I'm still a little scared about a lot of things, but at any rate
I'm going to try to get the best out of it.
I wonder where the sparkle from before went...
Cleaning
n Lee Motion
Motion
Bee
ảng
CM
X
Hey hey hey, that wasn't the end.
It was MZ Mom.
Oh my gosh!
That's so cool!
Oh, man!
It's so cool!
It's awesome!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!Thank you for your hard work!
Don't laugh.
When he smiles.
When he smiles, it pisses me off.
I'd pretend it pissed me off.
I was supposed to be pissed off.
I'm sorry. I laughed.
Thank you for watching.
Eonie.
Ohhhhhh!
What the hell is wrong with you?
me
Yay!
What? What?
I really don't like this.
Wait!
Are you kidding me?
Okay, let's play soap bubbles.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
What? What's going on?
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
I'll get the squirrel.
I'll get one.
I was thinking maybe a bunch of ojisaki or something.
I'll get a squirrel.You're going to be fed.
You get a meal.
Freshmen
Keep them coming!
I'll turn it over when I see it
Keep taking and taking
Where'd they go?
Where did they go?
Do you mind if I don't get the big one?
Not at all.
It's great that you're up for the challenge.
Is it good?
Taste good?
Yum! Yum!
It's great.
Great.
Oh!
Yeah!
That's great!
And?
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's like vegetable noodles.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like they're cutting up a pattern.
Sweet.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
You did a good job.Good morning. You did a good job.
I'm gonna cry.
You're crying.
This is the part where you eat the food. It's so tiny.
It's all big.
It's like the other way around.
It's the same as a big one.
I'm going to eat it.
Come on.
Are you okay?
I'm crying.
I'm tearing up.
Oh, my God, it's so salty.
It tastes amazing.
Oh, my God.
Amazing.
That's great.
You're getting so good at eating.
Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
I can't stop.
Yes, it does.
Why does he look like me?
Oh...
I have a feeling it's going to stop.
Ahh! Ahh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah. - Yeah.Yes.
Saved endes olabilir
precis
I hate this new idol
Unhappy coddled whole body ship
They're all busted up
The world's best 73 idols
It's important to be polite
The place where all the members' grandfathers are
Juggling music video
What was the hardest thing you ever had to do?
The Greatest Comedy Accident
Thank you for watching
Let's do it with our hands
I don't want to be this new idol
Mouthing off to the distance
Idol of idols
Yes, well, let's go ahead and go
There's more
Didn't I tell you?
It's useless.
But it's useless.
It's useless but...
Please do me a favor when you come out with your best
Too little money, skin care is a sticky type of natto
Petter.Petter
Troubled, troubled, troubled.
Demonstration in member's face.
Demonstration.
Demo.
The funniest scandal in the history of titles.
Quick!
The funniest scandal in Idol history is
Celebrate the 32nd point card!
Yes, we're up and running!
The most interesting scandal in the history of idols is
A big scoop, all the members are so excited!
The most interesting scandal in idol history is
3-minute cooking seasoned to the navel
the biggest role in the history of idols
Yay!
Yes, thank you!
The funniest scandal in idol history
I was caught secretly cleaning my dentures in the bathroom sink.
Oh, wow.
Your dentures are so clean.
Hey, then.
They caught me in the bathroom.
The funniest scandal in Idol history.
I washed up in the bathroom.
The funniest scandal in idol history
The Wen-Tung Challenge at home
Oh! Oh!
what the hell?
The funniest scandal in Idol history
The tragedy of not being able to get off the jungle gym 110
The funniest scandal in idol history
Oh no! Hibino's lover is Kappa Gonzaburo
Interesting! Thanks!
Thank you for your hard work!
I like the way you wear it!
Yes, but I had to get a little creative with the way I wear it.
Aah!
Aah! Wait!
Manamin's manacos.
I like the manamine look.
Are you okay?
What's the funniest scandal in idol history?
Selfie foot distribution in spite of being an idol!
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
Footie!
Good job!
Okay, we'll start with the next one!
Are you still going?
You're not done yet!
Enjoy the next video!
What's the cutest thing you've ever seen?
What is it?
What's the cutest thing an idol shouldn't say?
What's the worst thing you can't say?
Give us your answer once, everyone!Everyone give me one answer.
Not the prettiest... not the prettiest... not the prettiest...
It's too much!
It's too hard.
This one.
Here.
Yes!
That was fast!
The most un-pretty thing an idol shouldn't say.
Whiskey is small, right?
Why do you think so?
Here you go.
The cutest thing an idol shouldn't say.
Hey, butt!
Butt. My butt is my butt.
Is that what I think it is?
Scary!
Scary.
That's the cutest thing an idol can't say.
The other day, I got busted at a drinking party in Minato Ward.
That's great!
Great!
The cutest thing an idol shouldn't say
My daily aura at Yokoo, my inspiring routine!
Wow!
Yes!
The cutest thing an idol shouldn't say
Salary application
Why don't you just say it in a cute way? Like this. Why don't you just say it prettily? Like this.
Okay, everybody, let's move on to the next subject.
Are we going yet?
I'm going to do something that will make anyone who watches the Ruff Ruff YouTube channel cry.
Are you still going?
What are you doing? I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
Okay, that's enough. Stop.
It's like you're really getting royalty.
I feel like I'm in comedy hell.
The kind of thing that makes people who watch the Ruff Ruff YouTube channel cry.
I heard Hibino made you laugh so hard with his big comedy.
I bit it!
I want to say it again.
Okay, let's go Fujisaki.
A word that would make anyone who watches Ruff Ruff's YouTube channel cry.
Seriously, don't act like a father.
I'm going to say something that will make Ruff Ruff's YouTube channel viewers cry.
Actually, Sakuma's character will be reduced if he doesn't get enough views.
Yay!
That's great!
Who's ready?
Yes!
Oh, Sasaki!
A word that will make anyone who watches our YouTube channel cry!
I've already called all the seniors.
So when are you going to sell it?
Okay, Yoshimura
A word that will make the people who watch your YouTube channel cry...
He's getting blamed for everything when the camera's not rolling.He's getting flustered when the camera's not rolling.
How many more?
There's so much more to come.
We've been at warp speed for a year.
Korean.
There's so much more.
Wow!
I didn't realize it was a comedy camp.
That's great.
MV Where to go?
När ber though
glued to the ground
It's funny when you're doing something
A word that makes Otaku cry
Yes, sir.
Oh, Saito.
A word that would make you cry
I actually recycle the fan letters I get and use them as toilet paper.
I do, I do, I do!
That's funny.
Tama-less
One word that would make an otaku cry
Actually, the office is taking all the money from the checkered bag.
That's harsh.
That's great.
Oh, I can do my best!
One word that would make an otaku cry
Don't look at me!
Ahhh... Ahhh...
No, no, no.
A word that would make a geek cry.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
One word that would make a nerd cry.
My favorite restaurant is a private izakaya.
Oh, man.
I want to take the whole thing!
One word that would make an otaku cry!
70% of my LINE friends are young actors.
Ah, Yoshimura!
One word that would make an otaku cry
Yoshimura I haven't had a bath in a year.
Yoshimura That's enough.
Yoshimura Otakus have to say this kind of thing
Miyachika Then let's move on to the next topic.
Yoshimura, seriously?
Next subject.
Yoshimura That's not what idols say while making hearts with their hands. What did you say?
Yoshimura, you're an idol.
Yes, sir.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with his hands.
What did you say?
A friendly observation.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with his hands.
What did you say?
I'm replacing the sewers.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with his hands.
Yes, sir.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with her hands.That's not what an idol says while making hearts with her hands.
What did you say?
I had a nose job yesterday.
Smooth?
Yes, I did.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with her hands. What did you say?
Find the area of this heart with the length of one side being 5 cm.
LOL!
Good!
Grandpa, you're not that one either.
Let's turn over.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with his hands. What did you say?
I'm gonna shoot you in the heart.
LOL!
Not the heart, through the heart.
This is good.
That's not what an idol says while making hearts with his hands. What did you say?
I hate it.
Okay, let's go to the last one.
Last, last, last.
What did the Riffraff do to a national idol overnight?
What did Riff Raff do to a national idol overnight?
We got a mix.
That's amazing.
What did Riff Raff do to your national idol overnight?
I wished on a shooting star to become a national idol, to become a national idol, to become a national idol, to become a national idol!
Damn it!
Yay! Yeah!
Yes, sir.
What did Rough Ruff do to a national idol overnight?
I just realized I've crossed the finish line with a 24-hour TV runner.
Oh...
I'm going to sing with you, Sarah.
What did the Riffraff do to a national idol overnight?
They hijacked the Prime Minister's office.
Yay!
What did Riff Raff do to National Idol overnight?
They changed their name to National Idol.
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah!
What did Riff Raff do to National Idol overnight?
Won a gold face with a 3-meter dress just like Sachiko Kobayashi's
Oh, I see
What did riffraff do to a national idol overnight?
Caught by the public while freemitting in front of Shinjuku station
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yay!
Let's do it.
Did you do that?
Freemitter
Lunch is over.
Yes!
Yay!
Good night.
Yeah.U ha!
Can a heart star shoe become a semi-taihei mien? new series
I'm ana deswegen
Ilsa Gerther aa Please give me time to think about it.
I was a sparkling idol before, but today
But today...
It was hard.
The second half of the day was pretty rough on me.
It was hell.
I was wondering if it was all a dream.
It was just a dream. I just want to go home and let it in.
I don't know what I was dreaming about.
The sparkling idol from Logon.
Oh, my God! So sparkly!
Did you just finish training?
You're a comedian now.
You're a comedian.
Mr. Sakuma, let me dream a little longer.
Please.
Was your dream short?
My dream was short.
Let me dream more sparkling dreams.
Please, please.
Sparkling dreams
Sparkling Dreams
increase
Take all I have
Thank you for watching until the end.
Today's version is a crying version.
Please do.Please.
Please, please, please, please.
Please do.